<resources>
    <string name="app_name">My CV</string>
    <string name="objective">Every one searches for the BIG WHY.
        Why I have to wake up today and why I have to get out of bed this morning why I have to live till tomorrow. \n I have found my BIG WHY in programming and applying science beside computer. \n My passion is “CODING” sleepless night coding, solving problem and even find the bugs, \n yes I love to be tired, be under work pressure and out of my comfort zone.</string>
    <string name="user_name">MHD Samer Kador</string>
    <string name="user_job">Android Developer</string>


    <string-array name="skills_list">
        <item>Software languages such as C, C++, C#, Java, PHP, MySQL, Oracle SQL, MatLab, Prolog, Assembly language.</item>
        <item>Markup languages such as HTML, XML, XAML, JSON.</item>
        <item>skills in programming concepts like OOP &amp; Design patterns, Algorithms, Data Structures, OpenGL, Relational database and even in NoSQL database.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="strength_list">
        <item> End to end android developer, working throughout the entire lifecycle of building android apps. (System architecture like MVP-MVC, android components, Ui/Ux design, database design, Networking).</item>
        <item> Data structure, how it builds and work and how to use all STL.</item>
        <item>OOP concept specifically in C++, C# and JAVA and with knowledge of design pattern.</item>
        <item>Can work with GUI in C++, C# or JAVA.</item>
        <item>skills with problem solving, qualified to level three in ACM.</item>
        <item>using Git, SVN and version control in general.</item>
    </string-array>


    <string-array name="awards_list">
        <item>19th Rank – Ain Shams University’s ACM local Contest (out of 103)</item>
        <item>35th Rank – Egypt ACM National Contest (out of 120)  </item>
        <item>2nd Rank – Assembly contest Ain shams University (out of 100) </item>
        <item>2nd Rank – Intelligent Scissors (algorithm project, out of 30)</item>
        <item>1st Rank – QR code project (Image processing, out of 57)</item>
    </string-array>


    <string-array name="experience_list">
        <item>SALES ASSISTANT Baby Q Summer 2014 I have work in wholesale cloth office as an assistant for sales.</item>
        <item>ALBETAQA Freelancing August 2016 Islamic android app. Add services to an exits app on google play store to alert the user in a specific time like an alarm.</item>
        <item>TRAINEE ACM_ASCIS University community  2013 – 2015 Student community at Ain Shams University for improving and helping student in competitive programing problem solving.</item>
    </string-array>


    <string-array name="red_wine">
        <item>#ff670729</item>
        <item>#ff7a0c2d</item>
        <item>#ff96092d</item>
        <item>#ffa10a37</item>
        <item>#ffbf013b</item>
    </string-array>

</resources>
